Did the devil do it?
The Devil on Trial is a documentary, drama, crime film directed by Chris Holt.
Explore the first – and only – time “demonic possession” has
officially been used as a defense in a U.S.
murder trial.
Including firsthand accounts of alleged devil possession and a shocking murder, this
extraordinary story forces reflection on our fear of the unknown.
Father Dennis, played by Carlo Adamo.
Debbie Glatzel, played by Hannah Mae Beatty.
Self, played by David Glanzer.
Self, played by Debbie Glatzel.
David Glatzel, played by Foster Hamilton.
Arne Cheyenne Johnson, played by Adam Hunt.
The Devil on Trial is a 2023 Netflix horror documentary
exploring the case of Arne Cheyenne Johnson.
During the trial, Johnson's attorney attempted to use "demonic possession" as a
defense, but presiding Judge Robert Callahan rejected that argument.
The film explores themes of exorcism, interview,
family drama, docudrama, exorcist.
The tone is emotional.